profiles in holography is brought to you
through the generous support of the
international holography fund for more
information visit their website at
holographyfund.org
hello everyone this is Frank defreitis
and I would like to welcome you to this
latest broadcast of holotalk the
internet's laser and holography talk
show my guest for this installment is
California holographer Nancy gorglioni
now there aren't too many holographers
that could come on to the show and start
talking about their involvement with the
field going back to the early 1970s but
Nancy was there when it was all going
down in the San Francisco Bay area and
she has been kind enough to come on the
show and tell us her story which also
includes her work with Greg cherry and
their Company Cherry Optical holography
so you know there's not much more I can
add to introducing someone like this so
I will turn it over